Here.
It's a simple mission of figuring out a secret ingredient.
The two people pictured used to run a noodle chain.
One was front of house, the other was the chef.
Worked like that for ten years, then fell out.
My partner is the only one who knows our famous recipe.
Huh? Really? That's intense.
I was too naive.
I never thought that she'd betray me one day.
It's a real mess.
Figure out what goes in those noodles and your mission is complete.
So, got any questions?
Nope, I've got this covered.
Hey, how about you?
We're gonna need their names.
Right. Yu Xia and Lin Zhen.
Everything has changed in the back of my mind.
Your eyes.
There ain't nowhere left to hide behind.
Time no longer flew like it was.
When the flash froze everything before.
Without you, I don't know if I could take this road.
And I'm about to miss my mind.
Every minute that I die back in time.
Every single existence rewinds.
Some physical pain in a side drive all night.
All the headaches and the smiles never faded.
I know you'll be by my side when we make it.
Come back from the time.
Back in time.
Die back in time.
Plenty of clear photos.
But not many clues.
Take your pick.
Which one you want to try first?
I just don't get it. They were partners for a decade.
What came between them?
It's sad, don't you think?
Stay focused on the recipe. That's the job.
I wonder, if we were to ever disagree, would we still be friends?
Better stay honest with me so we don't have to find out.
It's almost time.
Unlock that frown off your face. Here it goes. Bam!
Childish.
Prepare yourself for another round.
I'm Paper. You're a rock. Game over.
Now who's the childish one?
Gear up.
Dive.
Stay right there while I make sure the night mode is getting a clear shot.
We've been working all day. How are you not dead right now?
Because it's our grand opening. So tonight's like our honeymoon.
Let's make sure to take a pic on this day every year.
Look through the photos on the camera. Quick.
You gonna make me wait all night?
We should wrap up. There's still a ton to clean up inside.
Finally done.
Know what? I bet weddings aren't this tiring.
If they are, I'll happily stay a bachelorette forever. I swear.
But our honeymoon isn't over yet. Come on. Up.
I was just kidding, dummy. You don't have to take it seriously.
Remember the dorms? We'd share a bed after scary movies.
Okay. So they were roommates in college.
No more jokes. We've served a ton of people.
It's time we feed ourselves. Noodles?
I thought she was tired. Weird.
Just get in the kitchen, would ya?
Looks like normal soup to me.
What's the secret?
Keep watching.
There it is.
Hey. What's that?
Like you don't know.
Playing dumb. Clever girl.
So, uh...
Anybody home? Delivery!
Come on. I'm not supposed to be parked out here. Open up.
Who is that?
Answer me or I'm gone.
What are you doing? Get the door.
Go on. Without those supplies, the shop's future will change.
I warned you guys. Later. I'm leaving.
Hurry.
I'm coming.
About time. You kept me waiting long enough.
Oh, so the boss is a lady.
Don't you have a husband to help you out?
Life would be a lot easier if he ran the shop for you, huh?
What? You think women don't have brains or hands?
Does that make you feel like a big man?
A real one would take this stuff inside for me.
Wouldn't he?
Uh, right.
I used up all the leftovers. So hope you still enjoy.
Dig in.
What about you?
I wanna watch you. Your face lights up when you eat noodles.
She doesn't seem all that bad.
Well, we shouldn't assume things. Some people change.
Old rules. We'll eat together. Like always.
Can you believe the stuff we used to cook in school when we were broke?
The weirdest veggies? Whatever scraps we could scrape together?
Our shop needs a signature dish. How about this soup? Keeper?
Nice!
We'll call it... Bowl of the Female Dormitory!
Whoa, what does she put in this soup?
This flavor. It's so refreshing.
Aw, poor you. Bet you wish you could taste it.
I'm good, thanks.
Hey, what are you doing?
It's not like I picked this noodle on purpose.
On purpose?
Yep. This picture's a dead end.
Let's try another one.
Your signature soup became famous overnight. How's that feel?
I haven't given it much thought. I cook because it's what I love to do.
In fact, I think the best memories are those that are tied to a meal.
Will you stop? That flash. If you want to take pictures, then at least turn it off.
It's screwing up our video.
Oh, sure. My bad. Keep going. I'm done.
The reporters follow her back into the kitchen if Elmer cooking.
Seems like a smart time to look for clues.
The audience will love getting a look at you in action. Just pretend we're not here.
Excuse me. It's cramped back here, so be careful.
Hey, you ready?
We're done here. A good chef keeps some secrets.
Wait, really? What's the point of running this exclusive then?
Another failure.
Here, keep on trying.
It's a really smart inventory system. Here, look. With intelligent management, you don't have to contact suppliers every day. They'll see what we need and deliver it automatically.
Yusha, how long has it been since you've gone home?
A couple of years at least. No time to visit. Too much work to do here.
So, is that everything?
Is that everything?
Yep. Thank you.
These are common ingredients. What could she be hiding? We're getting nowhere. Stupid delicious noodles.
Hey, designs for the new logo. Come look?
Yeah, sure.
Damn it. We still don't have anything to show for all this work.
Okay, boss. These are our newest creations. We tried out regional flavors from around the country this time.
Hey, thanks. I'm so hungry.
These are cheap, and we're poor. Now eat up.
Ma'am, you need a break. It's not wise to eat so many noodles.
No. We're going national. We must expand our products. Next.
I can't do noodles again. I'm seriously going to puke.
This is a new flavor.
I just had to eat ten giant balls. I never want to see one again.
I'm sorry. We're doing our best to figure out the ingredients.
The clock is ticking, and I've no idea where she is or what she's planning.
Next time Chao brings us another impossible case like this, we're asking for OT pay.
If she were to open up a new shop with those signature noodles,
the brand I worked so hard to build will be destroyed. I won't allow that.
You've been staring at this photograph forever. What is it?
Nothing. There's no chance in that one. We failed.
Come on. Just because you don't see a glimmer of hope doesn't mean it's not hiding somewhere. Am I right?
Am I right?
We said we'd take a picture each anniversary.
But it's been ten years, and we just have the first one.
Don't let this be the last. Do you promise?
Do you promise?
Wait. Lin Zhen took this picture?
Yes. Unfortunately, it's no good. There are no clues in the next 12 hours.
Listen. Please don't go.
You have fancy software, a flawless cooking line, and perfect packaging.
It's really not a place for someone who simply loves to cook. There's no heart in it.
You could at least try to adapt, you know. Haven't you ever wanted to create something greater?
The little noodle shop we first opened was my greatest dream.
But you've seen how much our business has blown up. More and more customers are getting to eat your food.
Please, Zhen. It's your cooking that makes them happy.
I'm sorry. I don't have enough joy to share. Not with that many people.
Which just means that we need to expand more employees and better resources to help you.
That's your dream.
Your dream.
You only care about expanding. The food no longer matters to you anymore.
And this shop is no longer mine.
Leave me the recipe.
Sorry. I don't know it.
Idiot. Say the right lines.
We're through.
That recipe is part of the business we both built. I'll sue you for this.
Fine.
I see now. She's the one who changed.
This is the moment where you're supposed to walk away.
Goodbye.
Where will you go?
Back to the beginning. I'll start fresh.
Well then, I don't suppose you're any closer to getting the recipe.
No luck. I've looked everywhere.
So what now? Any more chances?
Nope. She goes home and cries. The whole night.
She goes home and cries. The whole night.
Oh, my.
No, she's the one in the movies.
What?
It's not good.
Well then, I don't suppose you're any closer to getting the recipe.
No luck. I've looked everywhere.
So what now? Any more chances?
Nope. She goes home and cries. The whole night.
Good performance, Early. You can be quite the actor.
I always knew you were cold. This is so depressing.
And you're not helping.
That's right. Let it out. I've heard plenty of sob stories from behind this wheel.
Ladies like to talk to themselves after fighting with their husbands, just like you.
Complain all you want. It goes in one ear and out the other. Promise.
Xiongzhuang?
Oh, Xiongzhuang's a great town to visit. You should go. Not a big place, but it's absolutely beautiful.
And they've got this special plant called Fragrant Flower that grows there. Pretty to look at, but even better to smell.
Locals dry it and grind it up, then add it to food.
Wait, hold on. Does this mean what I think it means? Did we just?
Yep. I think you solved it. Fragrant Flower is a local specialty that few would recognize.
We know the secret ingredient. Fragrant Flower Powder. It's basically only found in one place.
You're telling me it's from Xiongzhuang? That's the key.
Yes. It has to be. Every clue points to that being the case. I'm sure if you were able to track a sample down, you'd see.
No. It must be. Of course. You're right. Now I know.
I know.
Mission complete.
No, it's weird. Suddenly, I'm craving noodles. I'd take back every complaint.
You wouldn't get it. Sad. You'll never taste soup heaven.
Go away.
Well, I guess we accidentally missed one.
Hey, wait! This is the background on Lin Zhen's phone.
It must have been taken in their dorm.
When the boss drops by, let's hand it over.
What is your problem, Loudmouth?
Delicious noodles!
Hey, can I go back for one last meal?
No way. That's an abuse of the power. You can't die for a snack.
Come on, just this once. I'm starving here. Please, I need them.
I said no!
You're like so smart. These noodles smell so amazing.
I never thought of noodles in a rice cooker.
Hey, maybe we should open up a little restaurant after we graduate.
Hey, Lu, what should I say here?
Uh, the future is full of noodle shops, so that would never work out.
We should learn intelligent management and how to code apps.
Huh? What are you talking about?
No, no. A shop sounds great.
You're right. Opening a shop sounds fantastic.
Oh, we can call it Xia Li Noodle Shop.
And it doesn't need to be a big place.
A small one is enough.
We'll work half the year and rest the other half.
Hey, wait. Here, look.
My parents had me bring some special seasoning we make in my hometown.
Yup, this is it. Back in Zhongzhuang, the older folks like to sprinkle the powder of fragrant flowers on their food to season it.
They say the taste can awaken a person's best memories. Isn't that nice?
Isn't your last Sam still feeling the wine customer?
The new clothes wore everything like to liquid skin.
I don't remember it's all drawn to this on mymonary
Smells good. Sweet with a hint of earthiness.
Hey! Don't make fun! Fine, I'll take it back then.
It's abusive, friend, you boys!
It's horrible!
Oh
Linzhen
Welcome home
Oh yeah, I nailed it. Practice makes perfect. Let's dig in.
I present my copycat recipe bowl of the mail dormitory.
If you try to start selling noodles here, I'm leaving.
Nope. No one's allowed to leave before the debt is paid off.
Yo, that looks good. Yummy.
Hey, stop. What are we supposed to eat?
hör
Mark
Pareto
想到十秒的电话没有接, 只需要在烟火下避震阳, 让周围灵后灯光退后斜细口下, 才能盖紧你的脸像, 将要坠掉
I got lost in the street that I'm living in
Or maybe I should just quit overthinking
I used to look at my hand
That's what I'm going to do
I'm not going to get lost in the street
I'm living in
I'm not going to be able to take off
You should really stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Stop stop thinking about it
While your mind overclouded
脱离现实的梦境化危机
时钟的我需要怎样才能自保
So stop thinking about it
Stop thinking about it
Stop stop thinking about it
While your mind overclouded
在这时间的风险停着思考
我明白多少烦恼都是永远自扰
Stop thinking about it
Stop stop thinking about it
While your mind overclouded
Stop thinking about it
片栗地
Guard